investorloft.com 2015-11-12

# Investment Property Search by the Numbers | At Investability.com

### Investability.com's Privacy Statement

This privacy statement covers the website http://Investability.com. Investability.com is owned by REIsmart LLC dba Investability (Company) provides a variety of online services for real estate investors and real estate professionals. The website provides a variety of online services for real estate investors and real estate professionals. Investability.com values your privacy, feedback and candor very highly. Any user information we collect is considered private and we do not use it or share it without the user's permission, except as permitted herein. We use this personal information at Investability.com to provide the best quality service possible. The following policy statement summarizes the protection and use of any personal information provided by the visitors of this site. 

This Website is intended for use only by adults. We do not knowingly solicit or collect information from children under the age of 18. 

### Security of Personal Information:

Your personal information is our greatest asset and your privacy is treated with the utmost regard and respect. The Company takes every reasonable precaution to secure personal information within both its computers and its physical premises. 

The security of your personal information is important to the Company. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can email us at customerservice@Investability.com. 

### Information Collected:

Collected information helps the Company better understand its users' needs in order to improve its product and service offerings. Email addresses are used to communicate with members with account information updates, news, and for site administration purposes. The Company may send promotional emails in the future, which users may opt-out of these email lists at their request. Personal information may be used to contact users for the purpose of research, product development, marketing, or customer service, if the user has opted-in to receive such communication. User search activity is collected and analyzed and may be utilized in the aggregate or in the abstract for a variety of business purposes. This information is not shared with anyone outside of the Company. IP address and cookie log data is analyzed to better understand traffic flows, user preferences, and to actively monitor fraudulent, illegal or aggressive activity. 

### Use of Information Collected:

Collected information helps the Company better understand its users' needs in order to improve its product and service offerings. Email addresses are used to communicate with members with account information updates, news, and for site administration purposes. The Company may send promotional emails in the future, which users may opt-out of these email lists at their request. Personal information may be used to contact users for the purpose of research, product development, marketing, or customer service, if the user has opted-in to receive such communication. User search activity is collected and analyzed and may be utilized in the aggregate or in the abstract for a variety of business purposes. This information is not shared with anyone outside of the Company. IP address and cookie log data is analyzed to better understand traffic flows, user preferences, and to actively monitor fraudulent, illegal or aggressive activity. 

We may disclose aggregated information about you and our other users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. 

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this Privacy Policy: 

  * To fulfill the purpose(s) for which you provide it.
  * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of Investability's assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Investability about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * With your consent. 

We may also disclose your personal information: 

  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including responding to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Investability, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### Use of Email Tools:

You may NOT use the Email The Agent, Email Listing To a Friend, Contact A Local Professional, Ask The Expert, Tell A Friend or other email services that we offer to send spam (i.e. unsolicited email) or otherwise send content that would violate the Terms of Use Agreement. We may monitor, track or save the use of this feature, but will be under no obligation to monitor, track or save these email messages sent from these tools. If you send an email using the Email This Listing to a Friend or Tell A Friend service to an email address that is not registered in our system, we do not use that email address for any purpose other than to automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. This information may be stored for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and for tracking the success of our referral program. We also do not rent or sell these email addresses of un-registered users. 

### Shared or Public Information:

Though every effort is made to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on Investability. 

Some member information is displayed in the following areas on the site: Listing Details, Professional Directory, and Professional Profiles. When a member enters a listing in the Listing Service, listing contact information is also entered and displayed on the listing for contact purposes regarding that listing. In addition, members searching the website can view contact information (name, email and phone number) when they view Listing Details of the property. 

Unless required by law as detailed in this section, or a user specifically takes action as discussed in this paragraph, individual user search activity information is not shared, and such activity information remains private to the individual user and to the Company. Professional Profile users agree to share their contact information and allow all site users to view their contact information via the Professional Directory or via links made available to users on a listing or in an email. 

Opting-out, editing, updating or deleting personal information: Email transmissions are used as a vital and primary communication channel with registered users and customers. As a registered member, you hereby acknowledge and grant Investability the permission to communicate with you via email (as well as other communication channel such as phone or fax) for any purposes determined to be relevant including, but not limited to, system messages, listing inquiries, product updates, service announcements and other important messages. Best practices will be used to honor customers request to opt out of marketing messages, but under no circumstances will the Company have any liability for sending any email to its registered users/customers. 

Members are not able to un-subscribe from system messages, listing inquiries, and account update emails which contain important information. The Company reserves the right to communicate with its users via email and phone to provide information about requested services and regarding issues related to their account. It is important to note that this communication is not used for marketing or promotional purposes. Requesting the deletion of certain types of user information may prevent users from accessing some web site features. 

Users who do not wish to receive marketing emails such as the newsletter or other non-necessary promotional emails, may opt-out of this service by deselecting the email option from their member profile. If you no longer desire our service entirely, you may deactivate your membership by sending an email to customerservice@Investability.com with 'Cancel Membership' in the subject line. 

### Cookies:

Cookies are used on this site. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. 

We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to use our site and to enable certain specialized functionality that requires maintaining information about your session. A session cookie is not stored on your hard disk and expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard disk for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following the directions in your Internet browser's "help" files. 

We do not store in persistent cookies any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

Due to the functionality provided by our site, the use of cookies is required. If you reject cookies, our site will not perform properly. 

### Changes to this Privacy Statement:

If the Company decides to change its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

The Company reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If the Company makes material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to customerservice@Investability.com.
